Selebalo Jeffrey Moepi

South Africa

jeffreymoepi@gmail.com

0661519713

linkedin.com/in/selebalo-jeffrey-moepi

Summary

I am a stack developer, with experience in web development, Mobile development and system development using different languages depending on what the application is required to do and gained skills in working with different developers on different projects both online and on-site.

I would further like to expand my knowledge and gain new experience within the workspace of professionals whom I will be able to learn from them and be able to share my knowledge of developing and coding with those who are already in the industry.

Experience



WIL (work integrated learning)

Central University of Technology, Free State

Jun 2022 - Dec 2022 (6 months) Created a web site with JavaScript, C# and Html5 which had an online database [Firebase] and a mobile application using Dart and Flutter with Backendless as the database



Laboratory Technical Assistant

Central University of Technology, Free State Sep 2022 - Present (3 months +)



Student Advisor

Central University of Technology, Free State

Mar 2021 - Mar 2022 (1 year 1 month) advice student with how to deal with academic pressure and assist them with being familiar with the institution and how it functions.



Senior Resident Assistant

Central University of Technology, Free State Feb 2021 - Dec 2021 (11 months)

Education



Central University of Technology, Free State

National Diploma in Information Technology, Information Technology Jan 2019 - Jan 2023

Licenses & Certifications



Data Analytics Essentials - Coursera

Skills

Office 365 Administration • C# • Python • React.js • .NET Framework • HTML5 • Analytical Skills • Microsoft Office • Stack Development • Team Leadership • Big Data • Engineering Management• Database [SQL]

Honors & Awards

Selebalo Jeffrey Moepi - page 1



Student housing - Central University of Technology, Free State

Part take in assisting with coordinating the Residence activities and making sure that the tasks of the house are completed while working with other house committee members.